{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"89.1/9.9",
			"answer":"89.1/9.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.693/0.77",
			"answer":"0.693/0.77",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.65/0.97",
			"answer":"4.65/0.97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.369/4.1",
			"answer":"0.369/4.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"68.2/0.031",
			"answer":"68.2/0.031",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.857/10",
			"answer":"0.857/10",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.8/20",
			"answer":"8.8/20",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.54/0.003",
			"answer":"3.54/0.003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.679/9.7",
			"answer":"0.679/9.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.05/45",
			"answer":"4.05/45",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}